<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-08-12T16:35:42-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">donutdeflector.github.io</title><subtitle>Web Developer from Somewhere</subtitle><entry><title type="html">A New Project: TEKaholics</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2017/07/28/a-new-project-tekaholics/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A New Project: TEKaholics" /><published>2017-07-28T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-07-28T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2017/07/28/a-new-project-tekaholics</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2017/07/28/a-new-project-tekaholics/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TEKaholics&lt;/strong&gt;: A website dedicated to providing tech news, editorials, and reviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It all started when a friend of mine, Traven, wanted to get back into blogging.
Traven had a small following of readers on his blog &lt;strong&gt;TheLastTechie&lt;/strong&gt;. However,
his last post, titled &lt;strong&gt;The Weak Case Against Strong Encryption&lt;/strong&gt; was on December 06,
2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traven expressed his desire to get back into blogging to the staff team of his
technology-based Discord server. I’m part of the staff team of course, how could
it be otherwise? :P&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Us staffers thought that starting a blog would be pretty great, so we got to work.
First, of course was the name. Eventually, enough thinking (and a wee bit of
circlejerking from my part) lead us from &lt;strong&gt;Techaholics&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;TEKaholics&lt;/strong&gt;. 50% more
street cred comes from dropping the &lt;strong&gt;ch&lt;/strong&gt; in favor of a &lt;strong&gt;k&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, Traven gave us access to &lt;strong&gt;TheLastTechie&lt;/strong&gt;, which ran on….. Wordpress. We
rebranded the webiste and gave it a nice dark theme. Perfect! Execpt for the
Wordpress part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Traven and a few staffers were playing modded Minecraft and hanging out
on Discord, I brought up Jekyll. Traven decided to check it out and then asked
me to migrate the Wordpress site to Jekyll.That totally caught me out in the blue.
Traven HATES all things hipster! Anyhow, he provided me an &lt;strong&gt;.xml&lt;/strong&gt; of the Wordpress
site and I got to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jekyllnow.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Now&lt;/a&gt; as a base for the website
and used &lt;a href=&quot;http://import.jekyllrb.com/docs/wordpressdotcom/&quot;&gt;this guide&lt;/a&gt; to
import the Wordpress content to Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I showed the makeshift blog to Traven and the other staffers, who were
happy with the quick load time and simplicity. Nice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That leads me to the present day, where I’m working on the layout and design
of the blog. You can check out my progress on &lt;a href=&quot;https://tekaholics.github.io/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of now, there’s lots to be done: comment system, author biograhpies, etc.
I’m quite happy with progress so far.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="tekaholics" /><category term="gulp" /><category term="html" /><category term="css" /><summary type="html">TEKaholics: A website dedicated to providing tech news, editorials, and reviews.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Pilot Post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2017/07/17/the-pilot-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Pilot Post" /><published>2017-07-17T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-07-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2017/07/17/the-pilot-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2017/07/17/the-pilot-post/">&lt;p&gt;Hello and welcome to the beginning of my blog. I’ll be talking mainly about
things in my life or issues I would like to talk about. Sometimes I’ll throw
in a few blog posts about web design or whatever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are still a few things that I’ll have to implement on the website:
commenting, a contact form, etc. Still, I’m sure that I’ll still be able to
talk about things in the mean time without much trouble.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="pilot" /><category term="website" /><summary type="html">Hello and welcome to the beginning of my blog. I’ll be talking mainly about things in my life or issues I would like to talk about. Sometimes I’ll throw in a few blog posts about web design or whatever.</summary></entry></feed>